easyhire.me 2016-05-09

# EasyHire.me - Privacy Policy

### 1\. BASIC PRINCIPLES

1.1 This Privacy and Security Policy is provided for the benefit of customers and clients of EasyHire.me ("Easy Hire dot me"), a registered service of Ekvind LLC, as well as other consumers and parties who seek information from or about EasyHire.me.

1.2 EasyHire.me is committed to protecting the integrity and privacy of personal information provided to its interview platform. This policy describes the types of information EasyHire.me collects, and the ways in which EasyHire.me uses and discloses that information.

1.3 Our Privacy and Security Policy applies to all individuals and entities from whom or for the benefit of whom we receive personally identifiable information (PII), 1.4 The EasyHire.me service is a professional website directed toward job seekers, employers and staffing organizations. As such, an individual must be aged sixteen (16) or over to create an account through our website. As such, the website is not directed toward children or minors.

### 2\. PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED

2.1 User-Provided Personal Information: EasyHire.me provides a platform enabling job candidates ("Candidates") and employers ("Employers") to engage in a live interview, and evaluation activities. In using the EasyHire.me platform, users may provide personally identifiable information. For example, in addition to providing standard profile information, including name, address, phone number, and other similar information, job candidates and employers engage in a live interview which can include dicussing and recording of information such as work history, skills, experience, abilities, work style and other responses to questions, and submissions of a variety of types of media including video and / or audio interview, coding questions, and the like.

2.2 "Cookies" Information: When you use EasyHire.me, we may send one or more cookies - small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer. EasyHire.me may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to our website. Persistent cookies can be removed. Please review your web browser "Help" file to learn the proper way to modify your cookie settings. Please note that if you delete, or choose not to accept, cookies from the EasyHire.me, you may not be able to fully utilize our features.

2.3 "Automatically Collected" Information: When you use the EasyHire.me, we may automatically record certain information from your web browser. This "automatically collected" information may include Internet Protocol address ("IP Address") or other device address or ID, web browser and/or device type, the pages you view on the EasyHire.me, and the dates and times that you visit, access, or use the EasyHire.me.

### 3.0 HOW EASYHIRE.ME USES PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED

3.1 EasyHire.me may use the information you provide or that we collect to operate, maintain, enhance, and provide all of the features and services found on the EasyHire.me website. We may use your email address to contact you for administrative purposes, for customer service purposes, or regarding content that you have posted to the site.

3.2 EasyHire.me may use the information that you provide or that we collect and/or aggregate to understand and analyze the usage trends, interests, and preferences of our users, to improve the way our platform works and looks, and to create new features and functionality.

3.2 EasyHire.me may now or in the future use "automatically collected" information and "cookies" information to: (a) personalize our services, such as remembering your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit our website; (b) monitor and analyze the effectiveness of application and evaluation activities; (c) monitor aggregate usage metrics such as total number of users, pages and media and features of the website accessed, etc.; and (d) track your entries, submissions, and status, including the ways in which you may interact with our service.

### 4.0 HOW EASYHIRE.ME DISCLOSES PII

We are not in the business of selling your PII. We do, however, disclose your Personally Identifiable Information in a variety of circumstances in the ordinary course of operating our business, such as:

4.1 EasyHire.me is fundamentally a platform for connecting Employers with Candidates, and as such, Personally Identifiable Information provided by Candidates will be shared with the applicable Employer(s). Automatically Collected Information collected by EasyHire.me may also be shared with Employer(s).

4.2 EasyHire.me may make available certain automatically collected and other aggregate non-Personally-Identifiable Information to assist such parties in understanding our users' interests, habits, and usage patterns for certain programs, content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality available through the EasyHire.me service, as well as to provide a variety of different candidate analytics, such as success metrics, uniqueness scores for submitted materials, and other statistical and analytical results derived from the information you may submit to the Service.

4.3 EasyHire.me may also disclose your information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright law), or in response to a court order, judicial or other government subpoena or warrant, or to otherwise cooperate with investigative or law enforcement activity.

4.4 EasyHire.me also reserves the right to disclose your information that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to take precautions against liability; to protect EasyHire.me and others from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses or activity; to investigate and defend ourselves against any third party claims or allegations; to assist government enforcement agencies; to protect the security or integrity of the Service; or to protect the rights, property, security, and/or safety of EasyHire.me, our users, or others.

### 5.0 DATA SECURITY

5.1 EasyHire.me takes the issue of protecting your anonymity and personal information very seriously. EasyHire.me protects the information it obtains about you with appropriate, commercially reasonable safeguards and security measures consistent with standard information practices. These measures include commercially reasonable technical and procedural steps to protect your data from misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, loss, alteration, or destruction.

5.2 While we do employ certain limited physical, managerial, and technical safeguards designed to help improve the integrity and security of our systems and the data stored on our systems, no physical or technical system, process, transmission, or storage mechanism is completely secure or immune from outages, losses, attacks, circumvention, design or implementation flaws, and human error. Therefore, we cannot and do not ensure or warrant that information you transmit to EasyHire.me will not be lost or compromised, either during or after transmission.

5.3 If EasyHire.me learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. EasyHire.me may post a notice through its platform if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach you should notify us at helpdesk@easyhire.me.

### 6.0 PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES

Please revisit this page periodically to stay aware of any changes to this Privacy Policy, which may be revised periodically at EasyHire.me's discretion. If we modify the Privacy Policy, we will make it available through our website, and indicate the date of the latest revision. In the event that the modifications materially alter your rights or obligations hereunder we will make reasonable efforts to notify you of the change. Our amended Privacy Policy will automatically take effect once it is made available through the EasyHire.me service, except that (i) we generally only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Policy in effect when we received that personal information and (ii) if you do not agree with any changes to the Privacy Policy, you may terminate your account, ceasing use of the EasyHire.me service.

### 7.0 CUSTOMER'S NAME AND LOGO

EasyHire.me may use its customer’s name and logo in advertising the customer relationship. 

### 8.0 CONTACT INFORMATION

To access your information, ask questions about our privacy practices, or issue a complaint, contact us at:

EasyHire.me   
63 Tyrella Ct.   
Mountain View, CA 94043

Headquarters:   
(650) 450-8361

Privacy Policy Inquiries:   
helpdesk@easyhire.me
